[Music]
with B Canal headed byal sales je
Jore together
win and recruit
Champion activating Champion Coro and
leader development Champion ay
Lola
wo
[Music]
[Applause]
n
sfwd let
[Applause]
W for the last time beat the now
nxf
W
[Applause]
stronger headed
by
[Applause]
[Music]
Ando get win activ
Julius
[Music]
[Applause]
Anda X
[Music]
FWD X
FWD us d x
[Applause]
FWD now can we hear your screen for
South
lard headed by J car all for together
with recruitment Champion
jpia productivity Champion Richard NE
and leader development Champion Ken
Manel
[Music]
[Applause]
s x that nobody me
sou productivity Champion Mark Fernando
and leader development Champion Adrien
kapio
nor s
[Applause]
l
no
on X
[Applause]
stronger nor
sarx F WD
[Applause]
recruitment
[Music]
champion
margand and
[Music]
Le
[Applause]
hfw
FW and XF
w
[Music]
and
now ter recruit Champion
Veronica territory activation Champion
David Fernandez territory lead
development Champion Christian
legasi head for Brer Bern
Sadona
[Music]
[Applause]
w
[Music]
oh
got
[Music]
on stage we have the ndrt C and
C
sing your hearts out and put your hands
together for FWD Elite agency team fill
my
[Music]
cup
on the horizon 2024
now it's time to go where Innovation R
10x Supreme a warm Round of Applause as
we welcome our speakers from our
management support team to unveil our PL
for
2024 starting with 10 x in marketing
with FW phpp Chief marketing and digital
business officer M Ro our abundant
B
[Applause]
good morning FW Elite Warriors happy
birthday F life for the we are 10 years
young and we have only just begun F
group was launched in
2013 while in the Philippines our
business started in
2014 10 years of continued commitment to
changing the way people feel about
insurance as a fan Asian insurer our
business P across 10 markets we Champion
customer Le approaches Innovative
propositions and user friendly products
we continue to make the insurance
Journey simpler faster and smoo on our
10th year birthday we celebrate 10 the
circle represents FWD as a whole it is
infinite X means more than you think X
is beyond a 10-year-old milestone
X is 10 in Roman numerals X is more in
multiplicity this
2024 we have prepared so many exciting
initiatives fif for our Milestone year
starting off with a Manifesto
campaign our aim is to strengthen F's
reputation and credibility as urer of
the Next
Generation Innovative inclusive and
people Centric insurance with easy to
understand easy to buy and easy to claim
products get Filipinos to change the way
they see insurance from discretionary
expense to a necessity they need in
creating their best future today last
year we've had our first ever Innovation
fest with media as the
audience this year our Innovation Fest
will be bigger bolder and open to all
this is where we are going to Showcase
FW service roster of innovative products
services and initiatives designed to
revolutionize the insurance industry
while contributing to nation building by
creating a positive impact for Filipinos
through financial inclusivity the FWD
brand is our most powerful asset and
most critical investment we can make in
our business to drive more chairs
command PR VES and set thises a off for
future do our R is what people think
customers FWD is a challenger EV and we
Pro it play a campaign that brought to
celebrate M spirit to
life this year we're taking it up Notch
by empowering our audience to celebrate
moving not just Sunday but today
introducing our 24 Grand
platform time to play an evolution that
empowers our audience to celebrate
Victory right now we launch this with
awareness efforts led by the Epic brand
fil and life rewards we can engage our
audience with online and on ground
activations imagine kind of drops where
top artists drop three lessons AR in the
store that dat sells not items but
opportunities
every activation needs directly to PES
and spaces where return participants and
Royal
customers all of fits every Mark
[Music]
budget we're making a highly adaptable
platform that make FWD a part of culture
anyone so let's start this exciting new
chapter and get our markets to celebrate
New
today
[Music]
wow we started off with our affordable
product called FW one it provides life
critical illness and acent protection
and th affordable again this product is
for as low as two CS of your favorite
coffee me you can already enjoy
protection for one month it comes in
different packages that reach the life
stage in budget of
our and this is part of our C more know
to protect our lives via a seall and
hassle SE protection plan it also came
with the first ever no premium increas
feature in the market which allows the
client to enjoy the same premium During
certain years when he keeps his fin next
off we launch our two funds the peso and
dollar P stop tivity funds we understand
that the pr time to get emotional when
the market starts Ming down and to help
address your draw outs and keep the CL
she does we introduce two new parking
funds to help preserve the earnings or
as a temporary parking facility during
times of vola and these are available in
both peso and
dotion and to help over more lives we
made our accident and critical ill
drivers more accessible by lowering the
minimum requirement so that more people
can enjoy the protection in room there
were also other inies like the aut
attachment of ourc riders our art Med
product extension and renal solutions to
five years the release of both for the
one and bory among others so these are
just some of the initiatives you work on
the past year now I am excited to share
with you what's in store for this 2024
as we celebrate our 10th year
anniversary and help F protect more
customers we know you're excited with
this type of product and and that's why
we will have our single pay product with
pay outs we want to introduce a new
dimension to our portfolio through a
plan with
G this new single pay product provides
yearly payouts over the course of the
sevene period provides protection
coverage for the family and you return
the single at the end of the maturity
period and the good thing is that it
will be simple to buy to siia or
simplified isue offer now as part of our
trust to provide protection to more
lives and to support the strategy of
enhancing further our BL
portfolio we are introducing a very
affordable rpbl product with a minimum
premium that's among the lowest in the
market it will come with the high
protection component and will have
Innovative protection
features in addition we will be
introducing two Deb benefit options to
give our clients the flexibility to
choose
based on
which the first one provide coverage
equivalent to the the A and the S while
the second death benefit option will be
equal to the higher of the
[Music]
e
down
[Music]
[Applause]
the other side of
us I just would like to
know orange balloons or
[Music]
[Applause]
Warriors
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
I started working when I was in my
second year college so from second year
college I am um independent already for
my parents financially uh I was part of
the Metropolitan theaters corus
metus and uh from then on I was given
from foros supporting um star eventually
I became um one of their leads and um
after that after so many years I was
looking for
something so I audition cultural center
of the Philippines and I got accepted
and uh that started my musical
career it was one of the longest running
musicals during the time which
[Music]
is augment my
income as a theater artist or
actor so I started doing the rounds of
the music challenges five star
hotels
and bread and butter and eventually I
got
accepted
[Music]
[Applause]
beginnings and then of course
King in
years actually
yes
[Music]
from graduates of the Performing
artsin us which is
[Music]
translation
so I was trying to look and for my goods
as an actor and I think that really
[Music]
started
performings I took all the voice lessons
that I can get and I was taking dance
classes in between shows I we were
of the week Wednesday and Saturday for
two shows in
between
[Music]
dance and I really wanted to improve
myself so I did
that and uh like I
mentioned uh I was a Lou singer for many
many years so will you allow me to s
leave with this song
[Music]
yes because there's a singer from
Iceland who made this song Popular again
and but because of her uh this song is
very uh famous
fortu
so
thank
[Applause]
you I
wish the bir
spr to
give
at that time uh while I was studying
industrial design University I was a
rockzz singer stud Jazz
[Music]
also and during that time a friend of
mine from the
oran kind of singing I have that
strength it's a gift
[Music]
it's and that was the time that he
introduced me to musical
theater
[Music]
mr84 1984 I
audition